Guide to the Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials
1961-2003
1961 2003
Glazener Dennis 1955-2010
Bell Richard C. 1928-
MC 00084
The Richard C. Bell Drawings and Other Materials, 1961-2003, document the professional activities of landscape architect Richard C. Bell. The collection consists of landscape plans and planting details, prospective elevations, and technical drawings, as well as associated architecture plans created by partnering architectural firms. A small number of project files, which document both residential and public spaces, are also found in the collection. Bell’s projects include private residences, subdivision developments, municipal and civic structures, various businesses, and some two dozen college and universities.
Richard C. Bell (1928- ), a native of Manteo, N.C., received a degree in landscape architecture from North Carolina State University's College of Design (then, the North Carolina State College School of Design) in 1950. Afterwards, he apprenticed under Simonds & Simonds of Pittsburgh, Pa., and Frederick B. Stresau of Fort Lauderdale, Fla. At the age of 21, he became the youngest designer to receive the Prix de Rome, allowing him to study in Europe for two years. He became a Fellow of the American Academy in Rome. In 1954, Bell became a member of the American Society of Landscape Architects (ASLA) and he was elected to Fellowship in the organization in 1980. In 1955, Bell founded his first firm in Raleigh, N.C., and for many years operated the business from its award-winning office space, Water Garden Office Park. His son-in-law Dennis Glazener worked for the firm, and eventually became a partner. Bell Retired in 2007.
186.7 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Gift of Richard C. Bell, 2007 (Accession no. 2007.0343)
This collection is arranged into two series: DrawingsProject Files
Richard C. Bell (1928- ), a native of Manteo, N.C., received a degree in landscape architecture from North Carolina State University’s College of Design (then, the North Carolina State College School of Design) in 1950. Afterwards, he apprenticed under Simonds Simonds of Pittsburgh, Pa., and Frederick B. Stresau of Fort Lauderdale, Fla. At the age of 21, he became the youngest designer to receive the Prix de Rome, allowing him to study in Europe for two years. He became a Fellow of the American Academy in Rome. In 1954, Bell became a member of the American Society of Landscape Architects (ASLA) and he was elected to Fellowship in the organization in 1980.
In 1955, Bell founded his first firm in Raleigh, N.C., and continued to operate the business under various names from its award-winning office space, Water Garden Office Park, until his retirement in 2007. Upon Bell’s retirement, the firm was handed over to his longtime partner and son-in-law, Dennis Glazener (1955-2010). Over the course of his career, Bell completed over 2,000 landscape architecture projects, received honor awards from 27 national groups, including the American Association of Nurserymen, lectured on environmental design at universities and professional organizations, and served as a member of Raleigh’s Planning Commission. In 2008, in recognition of his contributions to the City of Raleigh, Bell was inducted into the Raleigh Hall of Fame.
Adapted from: Bell, Richard C. “About.” Peebles in the Pond: News and Musings by Landscape Architect Dick Bell. 29 June 2009. 18 May 2011 http://dickbell.wordpress.com/about/.
Richard C. Bell Oral History, MC 00197
The Richard C. Bell Papers, 1961-2003, document the professional activities of landscape architect Richard C. Bell. The collection consists of landscape plans and planting details, prospective elevations and technical drawings, as well as associated architecture plans created by partnering architectural firms. A small number of project files are also found in the collection. Works are concentrated in North Carolina, but projects from Virginia and South Carolina constitute a noticeable minority in the collection. A limited number of projects, typically entries to design competitions, are from other states.
The collection includes Bell’s projects at private residences, subdivision developments, municipal and civic structures, various businesses, and some two dozen college and universities. Well-known educational facilities projects include North Carolina State University’s University Plaza (the Brickyard), master plans for St. Mary’s College (now St. Mary’s School) and Appalachian State University, the Amphitheater and Lake at Meredith College, and various campus enhancements at East Carolina University and Duke University. Other prominent works include Fearrington Village in Chatham County, redevelopment of Raleigh’s Pullen Park, and Bicentennial Plaza in Raleigh, which includes North Carolina’s Legislature Building and the state’s science and history museums.
St. Mary's College (Raleigh, N.C.) Buildings; East Carolina University Buildings; North Carolina State University; Glazener Dennis 1955-2010; Bell Richard C. 1928-; Meredith College (Raleigh, N.C.) Buildings; Bell Richard C. 1928-; Appalachian State University; Guilford College Buildings; Landscape architecture; North Carolina Modern movement (Architecture); North Carolina. Landscape architectural firms; North Carolina Landscape design; Landscape architects; Designs and plans Public housing; Designs and plans Public buildings; Housing development; Designs and plans Architecture, Domestic; North Carolina Campus planning
- Drawings, 1924-2004
  This series contains a substantial number of drawings and plans for many of Bell’s landscape design projects. Projects include residences, school and university facilities, government and corporate buildings, banks, churches, and museums. The drawings include site plans, planting details, elevations, and specifications.
  - 2027 Two Story, 1964 (Tube 55)
    Jefferson Sugg, builder
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Cary (N.C.)
  - 6500 Falls Place, 1984 (Tube 772)
    Reproduction
    Site study, elevations, parking level, floor plans
    Bell Design Group; Newberry Truman L. Jr.; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - 8 1/2 Marina Village, 1973-1976 (Tube 803)
    Old Fort Macon Campground
    Bell Design Group; Atlantic Beach (N.C.)
  - 8 1/2 Marina Village, 1973-1974 (Tube 804)
    Existing conditions, vicinity map
  - 8 1/2 Marina Village, 1976 (Tube 810)
    Staking and grading
  - 8 1/2 Marina Village, 1974 (Tube 809)
    Rose, Pridgen, & Freeman, Inc; Atlantic Beach (N.C.)
  - 8 1/2 Marine Village (Tube 769)
    Boundary Survey
    Townes William A. P.E.; Carteret County (N.C.)
  - A.C. Plat, 1970 (Tube 53)
    Site Development Study
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Pawleys Island (S.C.)
  - A.I.A. Tower Garden, 1965 (Tube 50)
    Staking plan, planting plan
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Academy Park Condominiums, 1984 (Tube 570)
    Floor plans, sections, framing plans, elevations
    Cundiff & Associates, CPA; Winston-Salem (N.C.)
  - Academy Park Condominiums, 1983 (Tube 812)
    Floor plans, elevations, sections
  - ACT-3P-130-R: Aerial photograph (Flatfolder 15)
  - Adams Concrete Products (1 of 2), 1981 (Tube 437)
    Drive and parking staking
    Bell Design Group; Morrisville (N.C.)
  - Adams Concrete Products (2 of 2), 1981 (Tube 724)
    Landscape Plans, Product Display Gardens
  - Adams Concrete Products (Tube 440)
    Site Plan
  - Adams Farm (1 of 2), 1989 (Tube 663)
    Illustrative Plan
    Jerry Turner and Associates; Planned Community Development Corporation; Kimley-Horn and Associates, Inc; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Adams Farm (2 of 2), 1989 (Tube 666)
    Kimley-Horn and Associates, Inc; Jerry Turner and Associates; Planned Community Development Corporation; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Adams (Mr. and Mrs. Fred H.) residence, 1963 (Tube 291)
    Plant list
  - Adams (Mr. and Mrs. James) residence, 1962 (Tube 890)
    Fuquay-Varina (N.C.)
  - Adams (Mr. and Mrs. John R.) residence, 1962 (Tube 37)
    Construction Plan and Details
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Adams (Mr. and Mrs. Thomas F., Jr.) residence, 1968-1969 (Tube 66)
    Landscape development plan, details, staking plan
  - Aerial photographs (Tube 636)
    Aerial Photographs (Unknown Landscapes)
    North Carolina Division of Highways Photogrammetric Unit; North Carolina
  - Ahoskie High School, 1969 (Tube 164)
    Schematic plan no. 2
    Jesse M. Page & Associates; Ahoskie (N.C.)
  - Airco Industrial Gas Division, 1977 (Tube 512)
    Planting Plan
    Bell Design Group; Research Triangle Park (N.C.)
  - Alamance Tech Ins. (Flatfolder 31)
    Photographs
    Alamance County (N.C.)
  - Albemarle Family Practice Facility (1 of 2), 1978 (Tube 322)
    Phase 1 development
    Bell Design Group; Edenton (N.C.)
  - Albemarle Family Practice Facility (2 of 2), 1978 (Tube 464)
    Site Plan (enlargement), Site Plans, Concept plans, Floor plans, Isometric
    Cannon Design (Firm); Edenton (N.C.)
  - Albemarle Plantation (Tube 8)
    Carolina Benchmark Engineers-Surveyors-Planners, Inc.
  - Albertson Ward, Goldsboro, N.C. Stake, 1984 (Tube 413)
    Planting plan, details, staking plan, site development, preliminary plan
    Bell Design Group; Phillips & Miller, Inc.; Albertson (N.C.)
  - Alexander Farm, 1986 (Tube 712)
    Master Plans, Sedimentation and Erosion Control, Grading and Drainage Landscaping, Soil Types and Proposed Lots
    Shumate Paul Developer; Bell Design Group; Wilkes County (N.C.)
  - Alpha Cellulose Corporation, 1978 (Tube 135)
    Existing conditions, master plan and staking, staking - north end, staking - south end, grading - north end, grading - south end, construction details, planting - north end, planting - south end
    Bell Design Group; Lumberton (N.C.)
  - Alpha Cellulose Corporation (Tube 180)
  - Alpha Cellulose Corporation, 1978, 1981, 1992 (Tube 324)
    Landscape development at addition, master plan concept planting
    Bell Design Group; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Lumberton (N.C.)
  - Alpha Cellulose Corporation, 1978-1992 (Tube 325)
    Planting plan, master plan, construction details, existing conditions
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Bell Design Group; Lumberton (N.C.)
  - Alpha Cellulose Corporation, 1992 (Tube 90)
    Planting plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Lumberton (N.C.)
  - Alpha Cellulose Corporation (1 of 2), 1991 (Tube 326)
    Master plan
  - Alpha Cellulose Corporation (2 of 2), 1991 (Tube 327)
  - Alternative Location of Painter Boulevard Parkway (1 of 4), 1989-1991 (Tube 25)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Alternative Location of Painter Boulevard Parkway (2 of 4), 1989-1991 (Tube 18)
  - Alternative Location of Painter Boulevard Parkway (3 of 4), 1989-1991 (Tube 19)
  - Alternative Location of Painter Boulevard Parkway (4 of 4), 1989-1991 (Tube 20)
  - An Indian Memorial Design Competition: Sponsored by the Little Bighorn Battlefield National Monument Advisory Committee, 1991 (Tube 503)
    Site Section Plans, Monument Section Plans, General Site Plans, 7th Cavalry Monument, Site plans
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Big Horn County (Mt.)
  - Analysis of Creeks and Flood Plain Capabilities (Tube 644)
    Design Workshop, Inc.; Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Analysis of Creeks and Flood Plain Capabilities (Tube 491)
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Design Works Studio; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Analysis of Creeks and Flood Plain Capabilities (Tube 492)
  - Analysis of Creeks and Flood Plain Capabilities (Tube 700)
    Street Maps
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Design Workshop, Inc.; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Anderson (Mr. and Mrs. Frank R., Jr.) residence (1 of 2), 1963 (Tube 477)
  - Anderson (Mr. and Mrs. Frank R., Jr.) residence (2 of 2), 1963 (Tube 478)
    Staking, grading and detail plan
  - Angell residence (Lybrook House) renovations and additions (1 of 2), 1992 (Tube 340)
    Bermuda Village
  - Angell residence (Lybrook House) renovations and additions (2 of 2), 1992 (Tube 867)
    Main Level Plan, Upper Level Plan, Site Plan, Tennis Court Area
    Bermuda Village (N.C.)
  - Angell (Don and Vera) residence (1 of 2), 1983 (Tube 54)
    Planting plan and details
    Bell Design Group; Davie County (N.C.)
  - Angell (Don and Vera) residence (2 of 2), 1983 (Tube 56)
    Grading plan, staking plan
  - Angell (Don and Vera) residence (1 of 3), 1982 (Tube 55)
    Section through patio and grounds
  - Angell (Don and Vera) residence (2 of 3), 1982 (Tube 712)
    Site Plans
  - Angell (Don and Vera) residence (3 of 3), 1982 (Tube 714)
    Elevations, Floor Plans and Details
    Ray Troxell Associates, Inc.; Davie County (N.C.)
  - Annedeen Hosiery Mill, Inc., 1982 (Tube 727)
    Conceptual Renovation Plan
    Newberry Truman L. Jr.; Bell Design Group; Burlington (N.C.)
  - Apartment Complex, 1968 (Tube 79)
    Flynn Ligon B. AIA; Richard C. Bell Associates; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Apartment Complex (Tube 80)
    Location plan, plan and section
  - Apex Commercial Village, 1985 (Tube 762)
    Bell Design Group; Apex (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University (1 of 2), 1978 (Tube 190)
    Topographic surveys
    Piedmont Aerial Surveys, Inc.; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University (2 of 2), 1978 (Tube 191)
  - Appalachian State University (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Flatfolder 5)
    Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Flatfolder 6)
  - Appalachian State University, 1970 (Tube 887)
  - Appalachian State University, 1987-1988 (Tube 888)
  - Appalachian State University (Tube 305)
    Conceptual land use plan, proposed changes, existing conditions
    Bell Design Group; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University, 1977-1978 (Tube 62)
    Proposed treatment - library network, site design, student support facility, grading duck pond development
    Clemmer, Horton, Bush, & Sills; Bell Design Group; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University, 1990 (Tube 269)
    topographic survey
    Mallonee Surveying; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University (Tube 269)
    Athletic Field, Aerial Photographs
  - Appalachian State University, 1988 (Tube 268)
    Continuing Education Center Additional Parking
    Wood & Cort, PA; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Broyhill Garden, 1990 (Tube 97)
    Perspective sketch of proposed garden structure
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Broyhill Garden, memorial, 1990 (Tube 115)
  - Appalachian State University: Campus cable television distribution system, 1979 (Tube 265)
    Schematic legend
  - Appalachian State University: College of Business building, 1988 (Tube 215)
    Storm drainage plan, layout and dimension plan, demolition plan, site grading
    J. N. Pease Associates; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Continuing Education Center addition, 1987 (Tube 217)
    Roof plan, Site plan
    Wood & Cort, PA; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Dining facility, 1988-1989 (Tube 215)
    Schematic design, site plan, lower level plan, upper level plan, topographic survey, elevations
    Calloway, Johnson, and Moore; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Dwight W. Quinn Recreation Center, 1987 (Tube 268)
    Landscape details and notes, planting plan
  - Appalachian State University: Dwight W. Quinn Recreational Center (Tube 278)
  - Appalachian State University: Housing study, 1990 (Tube 506)
    Site Plans, Aerial Survey, Floor plans
  - Appalachian State University: Indoor recreational facility, 1985-1987 (Tube 268)
    Site plan
  - Appalachian State University: Industrial Education and Technology building addition, 1985-1987 (Tube 216)
  - Appalachian State University: Industrial Education and Technology building addition, 1985 (Tube 217)
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000, 1987 (Tube 860)
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000, 1987-1990 (Tube 440)
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000, 1990 (Tube 685)
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000, 1988 (Tube 735)
    Conceptual Land Use Plan
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000, 1988-1990 (Tube 463)
    Conceptual Land Use Plan, Site Plans, Bird's-eye view conceptual site plan
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Halcan, Corley & Associates Inc; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000 (1of 3), 1987-1988 (Tube 540)
    Grading Plans, Site Plans
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000 (2 of 3), 1987-1988 (Tube 541)
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2000 (3 of 3), 1987-1988 (Tube 542)
    Conceptual Land-Use Plan, Planting and Duck Pond
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plan Year 2010, 1979-1990 (Tube 734)
    Site Plans, Conceptual Site Study, Bird's-Eye View of West Campus, Bird's-Eye View of East Campus, Master Site Development, Boone Thoroughfare Plan, Conceptual Land Use Plans, Spirit Bell Concept Plan
    North Carolina Division of Highways; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plans Years 2000 and 2010, 1987 (Flatfolder 22)
    Conceptual land-use plan
  - Appalachian State University: Master Plans Years 2000 and 2010, 1987-1988 (Tube 502)
    Conceptual land-use plans, Final study of Campus Center, Color site plan, site plans, Rivers Parkway sketches
  - Appalachian State University: Master Year Plan, 1990 (Tube 686)
    Bird's-eye view of outer west campus, campus concept plan
  - Appalachian State University: Music building, 1983 (Tube 217)
    Site and grading plan, site utilities and storm drainage
  - Appalachian State University: Plemmons Student Union addition, 1990 (Tube 217)
    Site plan, landscape plan, first floor plan
    Dellinger Lee Nichols Assoc., PA; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Residence hall, 1977 (Tube 472)
    Erosion and sedimentation control plan, planting plan, topographic maps
  - Appalachian State University: Rivers Street parking facilities, 1989 (Tube 267)
  - Appalachian State University: Student Activities Center, 1990-1991 (Tube 207)
    Entrance/drive relocation, utility plan, site plan, east and west access to arena, planting plan, lower parking lot, landscape planting plan
    Halcan, Corley & Associates Inc; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Student Activities Center, 1988-1990 (Tube 208)
    Planting plan, east and west access to arena, lower parking lot, floor plan, enlarged first level plan, east and west elevations, north and south elevations, site plan
  - Appalachian State University: Underground electrical and telephone distribution (1 of 2), 1971 (Tube 266)
    Southeastern Consulting Engineers, Inc.; Boone (N.C.)
  - Appalachian State University: Underground electrical and telephone distribution (2 of 2), 1971 (Tube 267)
  - Appalachian State University: Water improvements, Phase I, 1969-1970 (Tube 265)
    Moore, Gardner and Associates, Inc.; Boone (N.C.)
  - Arbor Villa Apartments, 1961 (Tube 169)
    Details
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Cary (N.C.)
  - Arcadia Woods, 1990 (Tube 252)
    Townhouse floor plan
  - Arcadia Woods at Guilford College (1 of 3), 1990 (Tube 128)
    Plans and elevations of proposed residential units, signage and lighting, townhouse elevations
  - Arcadia Woods at Guilford College (2 of 3), 1990 (Tube 130)
    Development plan, sign
  - Arcadia Woods at Guilford College (3 of 3), 1990 (Tube 447)
    Plans & Elevations of Proposed Residential Units I, J, K, & L, Unit L, Unit J, Signage and Lighting
    Dick Bell Sustainable Environments; Bell-Glazener Design Group; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - Arcadia Woods at Guilford College, 1986-1990 (Tube 448)
    Site Plans, Preliminary Plan Site & Utility Plan, Plans and Elevations of Proposed Residential Unites I, J, K, & L, Development Plan for Lots
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Evans Engineering, Inc.; Greensboro (N.C.)
  - ARISTA Information Systems Inc., 1972 (Tube 31)
    Ligon B. Flynn Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Winston-Salem (N.C.)
  - Arista Mills Company (1 of 2), 1964 (Tube 260)
    Details, elevation, canopy
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Winston-Salem (N.C.)
  - Arista Mills Company (2 of 2), 1964 (Tube 263)
  - Arista Mills Company, 1924-1964; 1924 1964 (Tube 323)
    Site plan, plant list, planting plan, property map
    Winston-Salem (N.C.)
  - Arista Properties (Tube 67)
    Land use plan
  - Arista Properties (Tube 475)
    Perspective, vehicular traffic and parking study
  - Atkinson (Eric) residence (Tube 362)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Atkinson (Eric and Donna) residence (1 of 2), 2000 (Tube 150)
    Preliminary master plans, storm water management plan
  - Atkinson (Eric and Donna) residence (2 of 2), 2000 (Tube 363)
    Preliminary master plan
  - Atkinson (Eric and Donna) residence, 1995-2000 (Tube 151)
    Preliminary master plan, elevations, floor plan
  - Atlantic Christian College, 1979 (Tube 299)
    Planting at administration building, Woodard Street parking area
    Bell Design Group; Wilson (N.C.)
  - Atlantic Christian College, 1980 (Tube 303)
  - Atlantic Christian College, 1969-1974 (Tube 67)
    Meditation chapel, parking plan, details of piers and cross bar
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Wilson (N.C.)
  - Atlantic Christian College, 1968-1976 (Tube 64)
    Service area, base bid, staking plan, site studies, alternate 2, landscape development plan, location plan, details C-2 area, planting, library, nursing education building
    B. Atwood Skinner & Associates; Richard C. Bell Associates; Wilson (N.C.)
  - Atlantic Christian College (Tube 862)
    Aerial Photographs
    Wilson (N.C.)
  - Auburn HD Transmitter Facility, Capitol Broadcast Co., 1997 (Tube 442)
    Bell-Glazener Design Group; Saint Mary's Township (N.C.)
  - Bailey (Mr. and Mrs. James) residence, 1954 (Tube 807)
    Plot plan, foundation plan, floor plans, elevations, sections, profiles
    Edwards & McKimmon; Raleigh (N.C.)
  - Baker (Mr. and Mrs. Julian) residence, 1969 (Tube 790)
    Landscape Plan
  - Ballard (A. J., Jr.) residence (1 of 2), 1984 (Tube 533)
    Topographic Site Plan, Site Plans
    Bell Design Group; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Ballard (A. J., Jr.) residence (2 of 2), 1984 (Tube 532)
    Topographic Survey and Enlargement
    Eastern Engineering and Associates; New Bern (N.C.)
  - Ballard (A. J., Jr.) residence, 1984-1985 (Tube 534)
    Grading Plan, Staking Plan, Master Plan, Site Plan
  - Barefoot Landing (Tube 551)
    Myrtle Beach (S.C.)
  - Barham (Mr. and Mrs. Roy B.) residence (1 of 2), 1964 (Tube 693)
    Sections and Details
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Butner (N.C.)
  - Barham (Mr. and Mrs. Roy B.) residence (2 of 2), 1964 (Tube 722)
  - Barker (Mr. and Mrs. Dan T.) residence, 1967 (Tube 721)
    Landscape Plans, Details
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Barnes (Mr. Carl) residence (1 of 2), 1977 (Tube 79)
    Staking plan, construction details, planting plan and notes, preliminary site development
    Bell Design Group; Hickory (N.C.)
  - Barnes (Mr. Carl) residence (2 of 2), 1977 (Tube 496)
    Plan of Pool at Patio, Preliminary Site Development
  - Barrett (Mr. and Mrs. Homer) residence, 1963 (Tube 499)
    Bell Richard C. 1928-; Fayetteville (N.C.)
  - Barrus (Mr. A.K., Jr.) residence, 1970 (Tube 790)
    Well Elevations Studies and Revisions
    Richard C. Bell Associates; Kinston (N.C.)
  - Barrus (Mr. Alban K.) residence, 1970 (Tube 813)
    Landscape development, planting plan
  - Barrus (Mr. Alban K.) residence, 1969 (Tube 458)
    Preliminary Landscape Development Plan, Supplementary Landscape Drawing #1
    William C. Harvey & Associates, Inc.; Richard C. Bell Associates; Kinston (N.C.)
  - Base Post Office M.C.B., 1969 (Tube 703)
    Proposed Grading Plan